Nice work completing lesson three.
عمل رائع في إكمال الدرس الثالث.
At this point you've seen almost everything there is to see in ES6.
عند هذه المرحلة، قد رأيتم معظم الأشياء التي يمكن رؤيتها في تحديث ES6.
But we still have one more lesson.
لكن ما زال لدينا درس آخر.
You'd think that with all the advancements to Javascript that you'd be able
ستعتقدون أنه مع كل التطورات التي تطرأ على Javascript، سيكون بمقدوركم
to start using every new feature in ES6, right now.
البدء في استخدام كل الميزات الجديدة في تحديث ES6 على الفور.
But that's not really the case.
ولكن في الحقيقة الأمر ليس كذلك.
Sometimes there are situations where browsers haven't
توجد أحيانًا حالات لم يتم فيها تحديث المستعرضات
quite caught up to the latest and greatest features in Javascript.
تمامًا بأحدث الميزات في Javascript وأفضلها.
In Lesson 4 you'll see how in spite of this you can still write ES6 code that
وفي الدرس 4، سترون أنه رغم كل ذلك، لا يزال بإمكانكم كتابة التعليمة البرمجية الخاصة بتحديث ES6
is future proof for when browsers catch
والتي تمثل إثباتًا مستقبليًا لموعد تحديث المستعرضات
up but will still work for browsers that aren't quite up to snuff.
ولكن ستظل تعمل مع المستعرضات التي لا تحقق المعيار المطلوب تمامًا.
Let's put what you've learned to good use in the next lesson.
فهيا نطبق ما تعلمتموه في الدرس القادم.